A Guide to the Peter F. Geithner papers FA1408
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professional and personal files, first run, 1963-2004; 1; 23.73 Cubic Feet About 57 LTR size Hollinger boxes, 1 Half-LTR size Hollinger box, and 4 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - Clemente Holdings (Asia) Ltd. (CHA) Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 June 24 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Clemente Holdings (Asia) Ltd. (CHA) Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 May (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Harvard University Asia Center, 1994-1999; Some material was removed from the file during processing because of suspected mold growth. (Box 11, Folder 132-135)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Food Security Seminar Series, 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 136-138)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Food Security Seminar Series, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) - Trustees, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Finance Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 141-142)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Annual Meeting of Trustees, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 143-144)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Asia Trip/Vietnam Visit of Ford Foundation Trustees, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 145-146)
  - Harvard University Conference - Conflict or Convergence: Global Perspectives on War, Peace, and International Order, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 147-148)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Asia Trip - Vietnam Sub-Trip, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Asia Trip - Bangladesh Sub-Trip, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Asia Trip, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Asia Trip, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 152-154)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Field Visit Briefing Book for Thailand, Bangladesh, and Vietnam, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Asia Trip - Vietnam Sub-Trip, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Asia Trip - Vietnam Sub-Trip, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Board of Trustees Asia Trip, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) volume, undated (Box 14, Folder 159-160)
  - Papers and articles regarding international relations and regional security in Asia, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 161-163)
  - International philanthropy and the nonprofit sector in Asia, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - The Synergos Institute - Southeast Asia Survey Report on Civil Society Resource Organizations (CSROs), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 165-167)
  - International philanthropy and the nonprofit sector in Asia, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Philippine Strategic Investment (Holdings) Ltd. II, undated (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Briefing Materials on Clemente Holdings (Asia) Ltd. (CHA), 1997 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Clemente Holdings (Asia) Ltd. (CHA) Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - The Mutual Fund Company of the Philippines, Inc. (MFCP) - The Kabuhayan Fund, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - AEGON Insurance Group, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Conference on Natural Disasters and Policy Response in Asia: Implications for Food Security, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 174-175)
  - Clemente Capital, Inc. (CCI), 1995-2000 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Clemente Holdings (Asia) Ltd. (CHA) Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 June (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Clemente Holdings (Asia) Ltd. (CHA) Board of Directors Meeting - Supplementary materials, 1998 June (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Clemente Holdings (Asia) Ltd. (CHA), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - The First Philippine Fund, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 180)
  - AEGON Insurance Group, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Clemente Capital, Inc. (CCI), 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 182-183)
  - The Aspen Institute - Executive Seminar Asia readings, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 184-185)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Workshop, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Workshop readings, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 187-189)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Project, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 190)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Project, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 191)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Project, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 192)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Project, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 193-195)
  - The Aspen Institute - Henry Crown Fellowship Program, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 196)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Project readings, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 197)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asia Seminar Project readings, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 198-200)
  - The Aspen Institute Executive Seminar - Readings, Volume I, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - The Aspen Institute Executive Seminar - Readings, Volume II, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) - Corporate-NGO Partnership Project, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 203-205)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) - Workshop on Corporate-NGO Partnerships, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - Seoul, Korea trip, 1994-1998 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - Hong Kong trip, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - Manila, Philippines trip, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia trip, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - Jakarta, Indonesia trip, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - Singapore trip, 1995-1999 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - Bangkok, Thailand trip, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - Vietnam trip, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 - China trip, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Institute of Southeast Asian Studies (ISEAS) 30th Anniversary Conference, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Bangkok, Thailand Office, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - East Africa trip, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - Pink Beach Club - Bermuda, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - United States Institute of Peace (USIP), 1998 (Box 18, Folder 220-221)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Bellagio Retreat, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 222)
  - Workshop on the Central Economic Reform Issues Facing China - Salem, Massachusetts, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 223)
  - Fourth Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) Roundtable: Regional Cooperation and Asian Recovery, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 224)
  - Gustavus Adolphus Lutheran Church, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Strengthening Civil Society Resource Organizations/Foundations (CSROs) in Southeast Asia, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 226)
  - Tokyo, Japan trip, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Tokyo Volunteer Center Symposium - Creating a Global Civil Society, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Tokyo Volunteer Center Symposium, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - College of Staten Island - Proposed talk, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Asia Society Annual Corporate Conference, Hong Kong, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 231-232)
  - Comments on Masami Tashiro's Article, "Citizens' Activities and NPOs in Japan", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Woman's Club of Larchmont, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - GAP conference - Manila, Philippines, circa 1998 (Box 19, Folder 235)
    Original folder was empty of content.
  - Harvard University Fairbank Center for East Asian Research Second Annual Conference on Democracy on Both Sides of the Taiwan Strait, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 236)
  - H.R.H. Princess Maha Chakri Sirindhorn of Thailand visit to Harvard University, 1997-1998; File includes a still image that was placed inside of a card addressed to Peter F. Geithner from H.R.H. Princess Maha Chakri Sirindhorn of Thailand. The photograph depicts Geithner, Sirindhorn, and a few other individuals and is dated January 27, 1998. (Box 19, Folder 237)
  - H.R.H. Princess Maha Chakri Sirinhorn of Thailand card, 1998 April 17 (Box 143, Folder 1853)
    Restricted.
    Access copy is available in orginal file: Series 1, File - H.R.H Princess Maha Chakri Sirindhorn of Thailand visit to Harvard University, 1997-1998(Folder 237).
  - Far Eastern Economic Review, 1997 January 23 (Box 19, Folder 238)
  - CP Group Chairman Dhanin Chearavanont and H.R.H. Princess Maha Chakri Sirindhorn of Thailand visits to Harvard University, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 239-240)
  - Harvard University Asia Center Week, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 241)
  - Harvard University Asia Center, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 242)
  - An Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow - The Asian Crisis: Meeting the Challenge of Human Security, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 243)
  - U.S. Environmental Priorities in China: A Dialogue with American Foundations, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 244)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Members' and Board of Directors Meetings, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 245)
  - Tokyo, Japan trip - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) and Sasakawa Peace Foundation (SPF), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 246)
  - Lingan Lunch - China's Political Climate, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 247)
  - Bangkok, Thailand trip, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 248)
  - Tokyo, Japan trip, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 249)
  - Republic of Korea/World Bank International Conference on Democracy, Market Economy, and Development, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 250-252)
  - Republic of Korea/World Bank International Conference on Democracy, Market Economy, and Development, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 253)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21 Planning Meeting and papers related to the 1997 Asian financial crisis, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 254-255)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 256)
  - China Youth Development Foundation (CYDF) - International Conference on the Development of the Non-profit Organizations and the China Project Hope, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 257-260)
  - China Youth Development Foundation (CYDF) - International Conference on the Development of the Non-profit Organizations and the China Project Hope, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 261)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) - China-Japan-U.S. trilateral relationship, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 262-265)
  - China-Japan-U.S. Trilateral Project meetings, 1998-2000 (Box 21, Folder 266)
  - The Center for U.S.-China Arts Exchange (CUSCAE) - Leadership Conference on Conservancy and Development, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 267-269)
  - The Center for U.S.-China Arts Exchange (CUSCAE) - Leadership Conference on Conservancy and Development, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 270)
  - The Center for U.S.-China Arts Exchange (CUSCAE) - Leadership Conference on Conservancy and Development, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 271-272)
  - Lijiang, China travel brochure, undated (Box 22, Folder 273)
  - Washington D.C. trip, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Nairobi, Kenya Office, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 275)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Nairobi, Kenya Office, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 276)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Nairobi, Kenya Office, 1994-1999 (Box 22, Folder 277)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Nairobi, Kenya visit memos, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 278)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) Conference on Corporate-NGO Partnership in Asia Pacific, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 279-280)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) - Conference on Corporate-NGO partnership in Asia Pacific, 1995-1999 (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - T.C. Hsu lunch, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 282)
  - Koichi Kato dinner, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - V. A. Pai Panandiker lunch, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 285)
  - Second Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow: Promoting Sustainable Development and Human Security, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 286-290)
  - Second Intellectual Dialogue on Building Asia's Tomorrow: Promoting Sustainable Development and Human Security, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 291)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 292)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Bellagio Retreat, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 293)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Spring meeting, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 294)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation (SPF) - Tokyo, Japan trip, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 295)
  - Tokyo, Japan trip, 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Thailand trip, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - The Center for U.S.-China Arts Exchange (CUSCAE) - Leadership Conference on Conservancy and Development, 1995-1999 (Box 24, Folder 298-300)
  - The Aspen Institute, 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 301)
  - The Aspen Institute - Asian Core Seminar Workshop, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 302)
  - China Youth Development Foundation (CYDF) - International Conference on the Development of the Non-profit Organizations and the China Project Hope, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 303)
  - International Conference on the Non Profit Sector and Development - Beijing, China, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 304)
  - Harvard University Asia-Pacific Policy Program, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 305)
  - Harvard University Asia Pacific Regional Governance Workshop series, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 306)
  - Harvard University Asia Pacific Regional Governance Workshop series, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 307)
  - Harvard University Asia Pacific Regional Governance Workshop series, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 308)
  - Harvard University Asia Pacific Regional Governance Workshop series, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 309)
  - Harvard University Asia Pacific Regional Governance Workshop series, 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 310)
  - Harvard University Asia Pacific Regional Governance Workshop series, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 311)
  - Dartmouth College 2000 Alumni Fund (Box 25, Folder 312)
    Restricted – financial material.
  - Dartmouth College Class of 1954 45th Reunion, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 313)
  - Dartmouth College Class of 1954 40th Reunion, 1993-1998 (Box 25, Folder 314)
  - Dartmouth College Alumni Fund, 1979-1997 (Box 25, Folder 315)
  - Harvard University Korea Institute, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 316)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Annual Members' Meeting, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 317)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors' Meeting, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 318)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR), 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 319)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors' Meeting, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 320-321)
  - Comments on Navnita Chadha Behera's monograph Engaging Tomorrow: The Ford Foundation and South Asian Security, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 322)
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office - 50th Anniversary Monograph authors, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 323)
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office report - Toward a Program in Public Planning and Management, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 324-325)
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office, 1975-2001 (Box 26, Folder 326)
  - Ford Foundation Monograph Authors Meeting - Monograph drafts, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 327-329)
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office - 50th Anniversary Monograph drafts, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 330)
  - Berkeley-Harvard Center for Labor Politics in the Pacific Rim, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 331)
  - Harvard University - Information Infrastructure Project (IIP), 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 332)
  - Harvard University - Information Infrastructure Project (IIP), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 333)
  - Harvard University - Religion and economic development in Asia, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 334)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Religion, Economics, and Politics in Contemporary Asia seminars, 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 335)
  - Harvard University - Project on New Institutionalism in Asia, 1996-2001 (Box 27, Folder 336-338)
  - International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia - Seoul, Korea, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 339)
  - International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia Sponsors' Meeting, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 340)
  - Philippine Country Meeting for the International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia - Workshop Report, 1997 August (Box 27, Folder 341)
  - Canadian International Development Agency (CIDA) – Official Development Assistance to the Philippines, 1996 October (Box 27, Folder 342)
  - International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia - Manila, Philippines, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 343-344)
  - International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia - New Delhi, India, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 345)
  - International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia - Taipei, Taiwan, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 346)
  - International Meeting of Associations Serving Grantmakers (IMAG) - Oaxaca, Mexico, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 347)
  - International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia - Tokyo, Japan, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 348)
  - International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia - Bangkok, Thailand, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 349)
  - International Conference on Supporting the Nonprofit Sector in Asia - Jakarta, Indonesia, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 350)
  - Beijing, China trip, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 351)
  - Tokyo, Japan trip, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 352)
  - Bangkok, Thailand trip, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 353)
  - Conference for Asian Foundations and Organizations (CAFO), Hong Kong, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 354)
  - International Symposium on Yunnan Upland Management (YUM) Project, Kunming, China, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 355)
  - Harvard University - China/U.S. university presidents' meeting, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 356)
  - Rockefeller Foundation expense claims, 1997-2001 (Box 28, Folder 357)
  - Harvard University Asia Center Faculty Grants, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 358)
  - Amartya Sen article, "A World Not Neatly Divided", 2001 (Box 28, Folder 359)
  - Japan Ministry of Foreign Affairs - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 360)
  - Commission on Human Security (CHS), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 361-363)
  - International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX) Selection Panel for China Resident Fellows Program (CRF), 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 364)
  - International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX) Selection Panel for China Resident Fellows Program (CRF), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 365)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Li Yonghui, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 366)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Li Rui, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 367)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Gao Fei, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 368)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Wang Xianju, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 369)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Fang Fuqian, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 370)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Zhou Changcheng, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 371)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Zhou Xuehai, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 372)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Pang Zhongying, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 373)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Long Guoqiang, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 374)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Deng Xinyu, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 375)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Fan Chunju, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 376)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Liu Can, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 377)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Liu Jun, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 378)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Shen Bilan, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 379)
  - China Resident Fellows Program (CRF) applicant - Kamil Tursun, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 380)
  - Citizens and Government: Civil Society in the New Millennium, a report prepared by the Society for Participatory Research in Asia (PRIA) and its partners, 1999 November (Box 29, Folder 381)
  - Global Trends 2015: A Dialogue about the Future with Nongovernment Experts, prepared under the direction of the National Intelligence Council (NIC), 2000 December (Box 29, Folder 382)
  - Harvard Asia Quarterly, Vol. 5, No. 3, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 383)
  - Islam and Civil Society in Southeast Asia, edited by Nakamura Mitsuo, Sharon Siddique, and Omar Farouk Bajunid, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 384)
  - The State and NGOs: Perspectives from Asia, edited by Shinichi Shigetomi, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 385)
  - Guidelines for Laws Affecting Civic Organizations, prepared for the Open Society Institute by the International Center for Not-for-Profit Law, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 386)
  - Japan publication, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 387)
  - A Common Cause: NGOs and Civil Society, National Foundation of India, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 388)
  - Effective Capacity Building in Nonprofit Organizations, prepared by Venture Philanthropy Partners by McKinsey and Company, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 389)
  - How Centers Work: Building and Sustaining Academic Nonprofit Centers, R. Sam Larson and Sonia Barnes-Moorhead, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 390)
  - Beyond Grey Pinstripes, a publication of the World Resources Institute and the Aspen Institute Initiative for Social Innovation through Business, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 391)
  - Global Corporate Citizenship-Rationale and Strategies, by David Logan, Delwin Roy, and Laurie Regelbrugge, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 392)
  - Fulbright Economics Teaching Program 1999 Annual Report, College of Economics Viet Nam National University, circa 2000 (Box 30, Folder 393)
  - Leading Public Entrepreneurs, Ashoka: Innovators for the Public, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 394)
  - Foundation News and Commentary, Vol. 40, No. 1, 1999 January (Box 30, Folder 395)
  - Foundation News and Commentary, Vol. 40, No. 2, 1999 March (Box 30, Folder 396)
  - Nonprofit Resources Publications Catalog, Independent Sector, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - Nonprofits and Development: The Challenge and the Opportunity, Institute for Policy Studies, Johns Hopkins University, undated (Box 30, Folder 398)
  - Funding Europe's Solidarity: Resourcing Foundations, Associations, Voluntary Organisations and NGOs in he Member States of the European Union, edited by Liam P. Doyle, 1996 January (Box 31, Folder 399)
  - Johns Hopkins University International Fellows in Philanthropy Program, undated (Box 31, Folder 400)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Center for the Study of Philanthropy - International Fellows Program, undated (Box 31, Folder 401)
  - NGO-Business Initiative, by Truong, de Reboul, Kempf, Kervyn, and le Folcalvez, 1997 December (Box 31, Folder 402)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Center for the Study of Philanthropy: Perspectives - Philippine Business for Social Progress: Can It be Replicated?, 1991 May (Box 31, Folder 403)
  - Asian Survey, Vol. 25, No. 9 - Learning from NGO Proponents of Asia-Pacific Regionalism: Success and its Lessons, Lawrence T. Woods, 1995 September (Box 31, Folder 404)
  - The Asia Foundation Working Paper Series - Funding Civil Society in Asia: Philanthropy and Public-Private Partnerships, Barnett F. Baron, 1997 July (Box 31, Folder 405)
  - Ford Foundation Internal Report - Non-Governmental Social Development Groups in China, Michaela Raab, 1997 February (Box 31, Folder 406)
  - The Synergos Institute Voluntary Sector Financing Program Case Studies of Foundation-Building in Africa, Asia, and Latin America - Philippine Business for Social Progress, Victor E. Tan and Maurino P. Bolante, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 407)
  - The Synergos Institute Voluntary Sector Financing Program Case Studies of Foundation-Building in Africa, Asia, and Latin America - Child Relief and You-Cry (India), Anthony D'Souza, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 408)
  - Ford Foundation - Worldwide Philanthropy Meeting, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 409-410)